So today I have the pleasure of teaching
you everything I know about claw code in
one video. And there's a lot of ground
to cover, but I won't just be talking
about starting your first project. I'll
be guiding you from the entire process
of literally creating a new folder all
the way to your application idea being
live on the internet with user
authentication and multiple AI
integrations. This might sound quite
ambitious, but recently I've had the
experience of multiple friends
approaching me and asking about this
whole vibe coding thing and some of them
specifically asking about claude code.
And this session is going to be exactly
how I would walk a good friend through
this entire process as a newcomer to all
of this. The main chapters that we'll be
covering here is one the setup and
applications we'll be using, two, the
agents feature within cloud code, how to
create them, what's their purpose, how I
use them. Then we'll hop on over to MCPs
again, which ones actually matter as a
beginner. And then we'll also go through
setting up your first database and
making your application not just
available online through the use of a
combination of GitHub and Versell, but
also functional by showing you how to
fix issues when they arise with a
combination of all the things that we
previously discussed. So, as you can
see, there is a lot to go through. But
I'm making this video because I'm
confident that you can absolutely do
this. And I'm saying that because I have
done this myself. I myself do not have a
development background, but with nothing
but curiosity and a little bit of grit,
I managed to really work my way into
this. And I'm looking forward to sharing
everything I know at this point in time
with you in order to get started with
this incredibly, incredibly powerful
software. So, with that being said,
let's get right into it. And the thing
that we'll be getting done today is
building a brand new application around
the idea that I personally quite enjoy.
And here's my idea. I'm going to draw it
out. It's basically a web application
into which you can log in. So, this is,
you know, username and password. And
then once you are inside, it uses two
different AI models to help you set
boundaries. Also, in other words, it's
kind of a AI tool to help you say no in
an elegant and professional way. This is
the topic that I noticed a lot of people
are not good with. For me, this has been
something that I was not that good at.
And as I got good at it, it completely
changed my life. And now I see it all
around me like people don't have the
ability to kind of assert themsel and
say no. So, we're going to build an app
that will help with that. And the idea
is basically just a text box at the top
where you can enter the event you want
to avoid or the ask that somebody's
making that you want to say no to. And
then what I wanted to generate is three
different versions of saying no. Light,
medium, and heavy. And then I want
images along with each one that I could
maybe send with the message to lighten
the mood a little bit. So quite simple,
but we'll be using the entropic API to
generate the free ways of saying no. And
then we'll be using a image generation
API to generate respective images for
you. and it's behind a payw wall so you
can share it with loved ones, with team
members, whatever you want. And I think
this concept of app is small enough for
us to get it done in one session, but
large enough to cover everything to make
you confident enough to actually do this
yourself because you're going to see the
entire process here. A toz. Okay, so
let's get into building what we'll call
the no machine. Yeah, I actually kind of
like that word. But in order for us to
build the no machine, we actually have
to get set up first. So I'll be
switching over to my screen here to
guide you through the step by step. So,
first things first with the setup and
all the supporting materials and prompts
and agent prompts that we'll be using in
this video. I put all of them into one
big notion page that you should open up
along with watching this video in order
to have all the links, prompts, and
resources, including the little tips and
tricks that I share in this video in one
simple page. I put the link to that in
the description below. I also pinned it
as the top comment. All I ask of you is
to sign up to the free newsletter where
we share prompts similar to the one that
this entire application is built on on a
weekly basis for free. So just check out
the link in the description for all the
resources that we'll be using in this
video and all the various applications
and various other recommendations. So
that's one essential resource. And the
second one is actually a video that I
already have on a channel which helps
you get set up with cloth code. In that
video I did my very best to show you the
setup from not having it on your
computer all the way to have a
functional version of cloth code on your
computer. That I won't be doing in this
video. Again, I'll kind of just assume
that you already have cloud code
running. In case you don't, that video
will be linked below. Go through that
first. I think it's like a six or seven
minute video and it includes some
examples too. So in just a few minutes
you'll be ready to go with clot code
running and in case you want to prepare
for the rest of this process. The other
things that you will need to have to
follow along this entire process are the
following. As mentioned you need clot
code installed on your computer. You
will need an enthropic account for the
API key from Enropic. You will need a
file.ai account for the image generation
API key. From there you will need a
Verscella account to deploy. You will
need a GitHub account to store your
application and do versioning of it.
Then for extra credits to make things
more convenient, I'll be using this in a
video. You will want to install the
GitHub CLI. And then finally, you want a
subabase account to host your user data
and the application data in a database.
The good news is if you set all of these
up once, you can keep building apps and
you'll just keep using the same
services. You just have to set it up
once including clot code. About the cost
of these, GitHub and GitHub CLI are
completely free. Both supper and
Verscell are going to be more than
sufficient on the free plan. I mean,
I've been literally running our website
on the free Versell plan for a few
months and I didn't even hit the limits.
So, that is free for both Enthropic and
the Fala API. You'll be paying per
usage. So, you'll have to load a few
dollars there. But, to get started, $5
in each account will suffice. And then
clot code is free, but the most
efficient way to use it is on the paid
entropic plans. I recommend the $20 one
to get started. If you hit the limits
regularly, you upgrade to the $100 one.
If you hit those limits regularly, you
upgrade to the $200 one. That's the one
I'm on right now. But I've been kind of
obsessed with this thing. A lot of 5:00
a.m. mornings and just having two free
cloud codes open, working on different
projects simultaneously. I only
recommend upgrading once you start
hitting those limits regularly, though.
So, start with the $20 one and avoid
paying through the API for cla code
because that just gets super expensive
extremely quickly. And for example, on a
$200 plan, you get thousands of dollars
of value in terms of the APIs. So, those
are all the things that you need to set
up. And I realize that's a lot. And I
also realize I'm kind of throwing you
into the deep end of the pool right
here. Especially if you've never worked
with any one of these apps. I decided
that for this process, it would not be
the most useful thing for me to go
through and sign up with Google into
each one of those services to create an
account. You can do that on your own.
And if you ever get stuck, you can
always ask Chat GPT or Claude to assist
you through the process. So if you're
trying to create a Versell account or
you're trying to do something in this
video and it doesn't work and you're not
sure about that one, you can type it
right into Claude code and say, "Hey, I
don't really understand this. Can you
explain this to me step by step or you
just go into chat chip and ask the same
thing and you will always get the
support that you need to get all of this
done. I'm confident in that because
again I've done it myself and also in
the community we've seen so many people
go through this entire process and set
it up with no prior knowledge. We have
nontechnical college professors. We have
entrepreneurs who took a software
development class 30 years ago in
university and haven't touched it since
picking this up building applications
monetizing them empowering their own
companies. This just works. And there's
a reason I haven't done a video like
this in a long time. This really is a
game changer and I can't wait to get
into the next section of explaining the
agents to you. Finally, now we have the
setup section. I'll assume you have all
of these accounts. You have cloud code
running and we'll just get right into it
by creating a brand new folder. Okay, I
have this folder here with various cloud
code projects. I'm just going to create
a brand new folder. Name it the no
machine. Okay, and then what I'm going
to do is rightclick the no machine. And
here on Mac, this is the quickest way to
get the clot code. new terminal at
folder down here and then you just type
clot. As I have it installed already, it
will open up clot code. I'll just make
this larger so it's easy for you to see.
Okay, I trust the files in this folder
and this is where the process begins. So
the no machine is created in a brand new
folder and clot code will be creating it
within here. So I'll kind of do this
two-tiered setup with the folder over
here and claude code right here. So
before we start creating the first files
in a folder, I want to show you some
essential things you need to set up in
here. One of them would just right away
be going to slash model. And then they
shipped a recent update here with Opus
plan mode. And this is just the best
thing ever. If you're in the lower
tiers, you're not going to be able to
use Opus all the time. So a lot of
people just default to Sonnet cuz it's
just way cheaper and you don't need Opus
in most of the use cases. Opus is just a
larger, smarter model. But many of the
things you do, Sonnet is perfectly fine.
It's extremely good to especially for
writing code. But in this OPUS plan
mode, what I'll be showing you in a
second is that before you implement a
new feature or you start a new app, you
always want to create a plan. And what
OPUS plan mode does is it uses Opus, the
big smart model with a lot of forward
thinking and planning and strategy for
your plans and then uses Sonnet to write
the code. So you kind of get the best of
both worlds without maxing out your plan
too quick. Okay, so when you have that
set up, then you will want to move into
initializing this project. And you do
that by saying /init. And if you say
/init in here, it will look at my
codebase. And right now it has no
information. It has nothing, right? It
is just the name of the folder, the no
machine. But this will set up the
project for success with claude code.
And you always, always, always want to
do this because the main thing this is
going to do is create a markdown file in
the root of the folder called clot.md
with essential information on your
entire app. And then as it works, it
will keep updating this file. You can
kind of think of this as the brain of
the project because really every time
something changes or you add more things
a cloud MD will be updated and here
wants a confirmation. So I have three
options here. I can say one yes, two yes
and don't ask me again. This command is
always okay and then free no and then
you can kind of direct it. I usually
like to say the second yes so it doesn't
bug me so much. And there you go. It
created the cloud MD file. We can kind
of have a quick look at this. This file
provides guidance to clot code when
working with code in this repository.
This repository is currently empty. when
code is added this file should be
updated with and then here are the
different things that will be in here.
So again this is kind of the brain of
the project. You can also think of it in
terms of human psychology as the ego of
the project. The identity like what does
it do? What is this project's job? What
are the previous employments or schools
that this project went to? What tools is
it using etc. So now that we have the
basic setup I want to get started with
this app. Let's actually start turning
the no machine into a reality by telling
it about our app idea. But before we
start typing we got to enable one
essential feature. You got to know this
and it's a bit hidden. So what you want
to do is hit shift and tab. And I want
you to watch this part of the screen
when I do that. Shift and tap once. Plan
mode on. See that? If I shift and tap
multiple times, it kind of cycles
through these three options. I want to
go to plan mode. Because if you're
inside of plan mode, clot code will not
be doing. It will be planning its next
actions. Because if I would just type
what I want from this app, what would
usually happen is say this is cloud code
right here. And I send it a prompt with
hey, I want the no machine. And then I
give it some details on what I imagine
with the app. Without the plan mode on,
clot code would move on to create a
to-do list. This is my beautiful drawing
of a to-do list with different items.
And then it will think for a little bit
and start working on the first item. And
then it will work on the second item and
so on and implement all of this. And a
few minutes later you have the
application right there for you to
review, add features, remove features,
remove any bugs, etc. We do not want
this for anything that is a big task.
It's fine to let it work like this many
times, but if you're starting a brand
new app, especially also if you're
adding any new feature, what you rather
want to do is have cloud code here, but
have it in plan mode as we switched it
right now. And we're going to send the
same no machine prompt idea to it. Oh
god, my writing is getting increasingly
bad here. And then rather than it
creating a to-do list and just getting
to work right away in the plan mode, as
you might already be able to tell, it
will create a plan for us and say,
"Okay, these are the to-dos that I'm
planning to do. These are the features
that I want to include. These are the
things that it's going to achieve, and
this is the architecture that I
propose." Now, you don't have to
understand all of the things that we
will plan for in order for this to be
useful for you, but you definitely want
to review its direction, especially if
you're starting with nothing as we are
right now. So, what I'm going to do
right here is I'm just going to type out
my idea for this no machine. I want to
create a web app that uses the enthropic
API to turn a event that I want to
decline or a message that I want to
reject into three different ideas on how
to set a boundary or say no. The
application will be titled the no
machine. And for each one of the three
ideas, I also want to generate images
that could be sent along with the
message you generate to get the point
across smoothly. Okay, I think that
describes it pretty well. And now I'm
just going to name the different models
that I plan on using the file.AI AI flux
realism API and ropic opus 4.1 API for
the response generation and a sappa
basease for the authentication.
And I think that's actually it. So this
is really all it takes to get going. And
now that we're in plan mode, I can
already hit enter and kind of explain a
few alternative approaches that other
people take because as you start
consuming content on cloud code, you
will find many different opinions on how
to get a project started. Some
developers have these elaborate
frameworks on how to exactly do it and
they're sure that they have the very
best way. There's these entire methods
with like 10 steps that you have to do
before you even get started into the
project. And although that might make
sense, what I found from some fellow
developers and cloud code users is that
a lot of them don't work reliably. And
at this point in time, we just don't
have a single consensus of how to best
do it. And this tutorial is for getting
your first proper project up and
running. So we won't be getting into
creating an entire PRD and design
specifications in advance before getting
into this. I just described this in
natural language in two sentences. And
there we go. We have the plan. In case
you wondered how I dictated right into
cloth code that's not a native feature
is this is a app called Whisperflow that
actually reached out to sponsor us and
we're going to be doing some
partnerships with them in other videos.
But yeah, this is not sponsored. I just
generally use them and it works great
with cloud code because I just press two
buttons and I can dictate just like I
would in chatbt or claude. Back to our
plan. So here we have the plan. You
really want to review this in details.
So the no machine web app implementation
plan text stack front end next.js14 with
app router TypeScript tailwind and CSS.
So if you're non-technical, you don't
really have to understand all of this.
But I think as you work with a few
projects, you'll just naturally learn
about some of these frameworks. And it
often helps to kind of just zero one out
and then ask for chippity explain
next.js 14 to me like I'm 16. I kind of
like the 16 to 18 range because it
doesn't tell children stories but it
really keeps it simple. It's like Lego
blocks for a website. You build small
pieces and snap them together. NextJ is
like a pro toolkit that makes React
easier and more powerful. Okay. And it
explains more back to building this
thing. So authentication will be with
supperase APIs will be enthropic cloud
and file AI flux realism. The database
will be supperase and will deploy on
versel. This is the folder structure it
imagines that will in a second appear in
here. And then these are the different
implementation steps. You can see
there's only seven. This is actually
quite a simple application for us to
build here today. So it will go through
the step by step. And now it asks you,
okay, do you want me to proceed and then
stop at every phase and do you need to
approve the edits or do you want to
change something about the plan and keep
going? Now we could just say yes, but at
this point I will show you the very best
practice that I hope you will have
learned and adopted by the end of this
video and that is using MCP to make sure
these entire plans are based on the
reality of what these frameworks do
today and how they're used today. Now
that may sound complex, but luckily this
is the most common problem and there's a
fantastic tool that you can activate as
a MCP and cloud code to actually get
this done automatically. Still confused?
Let me show you in practice and explain
after. Okay, so I'm going to say no,
keep planning and I want to alter the
plan. And what I'm going to do is I'm
just going to tell it review the plan
with context 7. And I'm just going to
hit enter and we're going to see this
work. What context 7 is is a MCP that I
have installed in here. It's completely
free. We'll do it later on in this video
and I'll be showing you MCP management
and agent management in a later point of
this video. But as I said, we're kind of
skipping ahead here because this is so
damn useful. If you're not familiar,
context 7.com is just this free website
that collects the newest version of the
documentation for all of these things.
So, for example, we'll be using Versel,
right? And they updated their
documentation 6 days ago, and the newest
version is available right here. And you
could go in here and copy this entire
documentation by hand and paste it into
cloud code. And you could do that with
each one of the actual tech tools that
you'll be using here. Or alternatively,
you just install the MCP server by
running this one line in clot code. This
is somewhere down here. We'll do this
later. Installing clot code. And if you
run this line once and restart clot
code, this right here, it will add a MCP
server that you can then invoke inside
of clot code by simply saying what I did
right there. So if we scroll up a little
bit, you'll see review the plan with
context 7. Aha. And then we see right
here I actually do not have the context
7 server. So I'll hit escape to abandon
this plan for now and say /mcp. Ah, and
it says no MCP servers configured. So
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
just close this conversation with cloud
code right there. And to install the MCP
again, this is skipping ahead a little
bit. You just go ahead and run this
command. And it looks like it added it
successfully. So we can just close this
terminal and open up clot code again.
new terminal folder claude. And now I
get to show you this extra feature which
is if you type /help, you see all the
commands that are available to you. And
there's one that continues your last
conversation where it left off. It's
/resume. Okay, so I'm going to say
/resume and then it's this one from 1
minute ago with 55 messages. Perfect.
See, it loads right into where we were
before. And now I can type /mcp and
hopefully we have the context 7 server
here right there. It's already installed
in the project. So now that it's
installed, I could just escape out of
this. I can say review the plan with the
context 7 mcp and now it has the server
to actually look at all this
documentation for all the apps again it
told us about in the beginning so as you
remember it told us it's going to use
nexjs sapper basease typescript tailwind
versel and now clot code has the ability
to on its own check out all the newest
documentation on those tools and adjust
the plan for how to exactly implement
this according to the makers of those
technologies themselves. And that's
really what you do. This is how you get
the best most reliable results because
often these LLMs are trained on code
that is a few years old and maybe
certain things worked a bit differently
back then. This way you make sure it's
all up to date. So I'm going to confirm
once more here. And from here on out, I
won't be explaining this whole
confirmation process. If you just see
this pop up, you can always either say
yes, continue or no, don't continue.
Sometimes you get this option in the
middle like yes, don't ask me again. And
usually I use that. So then it just
becomes a bit more flowy and easy. Okay,
here's the updated plan. So based on my
research with context 7, here's the
updated and refined implementation plan.
And then it tells you here are the key
insights from the research from the new
documents. NextJS app browser
authentication. Here's a best practice
on how to actually do it. This is
something it didn't have before.
Amazing. Sappa based documentation said
this is how authentication is best done
today, not a year ago, not two weeks
ago, today. Also checked out the
entropic integrations and the
documentation from Enthropic themselves
on how to use the API and then here are
the phases. First it will build the
foundations. Then it will build
authentication. Then core functionality,
image generation features and data and
polish. So one thing I noticed here is
we're not in plan mode anymore. So I'm
going to say shift tab twice more to get
back to the plan mode. At this point I
could just say continue. But I'm going
to go back to plan mode and insert one
more thing for our plan because I do
actually have a very specific prompt
that I want to use that I prepared here
in advance. I just had a conversation
about Claude with what I imagine with
this prompt and after a few refinements
I arrived at this point where I feel
very happy with it. System prompt
boundary coach AI. So this right here,
you are a reformed peopleleaser turned
boundary expert. You once apologized to
automatic doors for making them open.
Now you help others set clear
professional boundaries without the
guilt spiral. And then the whole point
of this is that you input a specific
boundary scenario and then it outputs
free boundary options, a soft no, a
clear no, and a wall, including free
image prompts to visualize that. I'm
just going to take this as is and copy
it into claw code. It even has some
example image prompts. Amazing. And I'm
actually going to copy this entire
message and tell claw code one last
refinement of our plan. All right, that
sounds great. I also already have the
prompt. I want to use to generate the
free boundaries and the according
visuals. Okay. And then in quotation
marks I just paste in this entire prompt
with commandV. And that is it. Now I'm
ready to hit enter. It's going to create
one final plan and we're ready to go.
And as that will work, we will move to
talking about agents and how to use them
in the process. But already with us
having this set up and being at this
stage, we're ready to hit enter and let
this agentic system do its thing and
build out this application for us. Now,
to be clear, there's more to talk about
here and we have to finish this entire
process, okay? But if you got to this
stage and if you followed along and if
you set up all the things, you're super
far already because this core process of
planning, refining the plan, and then
getting to this point where it tells you
this is the entire implementation plan.
These are the key features. We're going
to have free responses, humorous
visuals, we're going to have the
reformed doormat personality. I just
absolutely love that word combination
right there. We are ready to just hit
enter to build this. Okay, so now that
this is on its way, it will work for I
don't know, my guess would be 5 minutes
to actually populate this entire folder.
I'll kind of leave this on screen right
now and we can fast forward over it. And
I'll probably have to confirm this a few
times in the process. But what I want to
do next is review how claw code is
practically working right here and how
you can make this workflow even better
by using MCPs and agents. They really go
hand in hand, but I want to start out by
talking agents because we'll be using
them in a second here. Now, as you can
see right here from this entire
conversation, there is a to-do list
right here that it will work for. And
what clot code basically does in the
background, you can think of it as uh
agentic system that will spawn a agent
to tackle the first item and work
through it and then it moves on to the
second item and works through it. And it
has a lot of tools here. This is the
terminal. So it can create folders. It
can delete folders. It has different
search functions to look over the entire
application that it's building. Look, if
I open this up already, we have all
these files that it created in here just
by doing its thing. To be clear, I'm
just explaining right now, right? This
is running by itself. The only thing I'm
clicking is that if it asks for
permissions, I tell it, yeah, do that.
And if you ask again, keep doing it. But
it's already creating the application in
here by itself. This is not like chat
GPT where it writes 200 300 lines of
code and you can maybe preview it in
there. But if you start going beyond, it
starts getting lost. No, because this
has task management built in this big
old to-do that it's doing here and these
planning features where it uses the
super smart model to plan for you and
you refine the plan. The results of this
are far superior. You can build apps
that are thousands, if not tens of
thousands of lines of code that actually
work. I'm not saying they're perfect.
I'm not saying you should go ahead and
sell them to the world and pretend as if
you have enterprisegrade security right
off the bat. No, for that you should
probably work with a professional
developer or a studio to get it audited
so that it's all okay. But if you're
using this for yourself or within your
company or the stakes are not that high,
this works and it works better than
anything like this before. And I want to
be clear, we've seen many applications
like this before. This is not the first
agentic builder that has come out.
Matter of fact, there's been dozens if
not hundreds before this. I remember
back in 20123, we had agent GPT and we
had baby AGI. Remember those? They kind
of worked. Not really. Nobody really
used them for anything useful, but it
was the same idea. Let's not use one
chat GPT, but let's use five chat GPS
working together to get more done. This
is the first system that really
successfully integrated it and that's
why I'm showing it to you today. And
that explanation now transitions into
this discussion around agents which as
this works I want to illustrate to you
on brand new slide right here because
what you're probably familiar with is
the following when it comes to agents. I
will assume you're familiar with chatb
if you're watching this video like
probably have account and you've
probably been using it for a while. And
the way chatb works is well you give
chatpt a prompt and chatt gives you a
response. Now they started making it
more powerful in multiple ways. They add
extra context to your prompt. So the
memories dynamically look at your other
conversations and all of a sudden Chachi
knows more about you. And it's not just
the prompt that you're feeding it.
You're giving it the prompt plus some
extra stuff. You can set this up in a
custom way through custom instructions.
So Chachi is not just getting the
prompt, but then also they started
adding in tools, right? There's the code
interpreter. There's the image
generation function. Chachidi doesn't
just give you text back. It can generate
images. It can write code. So it doesn't
just give you the response, but here in
the middle it might use the image
generator that went so viral this year.
Then it gives you a response plus a
image and people are really excited
about that because all of a sudden their
AI assistant can generate images. It can
visualize data. It can do maths and
things like that by running code. It's
really impressive. Now how does this
differ from clot code and how does just
clot code differ from using custom sub
aents in cloud code which I want to
explain now. Well the base promise stays
the same, right? Just instead of chatt
we have cloud code over here and you
still input a prompt that it works with
right the fact that this interface looks
a lot less user friendly than chat GPT
is just a visual thing under the hood
the same thing is happening you give a
prompt to LLM and then it processes it
but the big difference here is there's
different types of context that get
added one so as we talked about the clot
MD file is one type this didn't get
updated yet with everything we want to
do with our project we'll do this in a
second as soon as it's done with all of
these tasks here but that is one piece
of context that keeps it on track. We're
not just working on a task. We're
working on an entire project and you got
to keep the northstar of the project in
mind, not just the task you're working
on. Beyond that, it spawns these
different sub aents by itself. You can
see it's doing these things step by
step. So, it has a to-do list and then
it spawns different versions of itself
to tackle those things and then it
prompts itself on the background. So,
they didn't fully reveal this. There's
people studying this and using proxy
servers to kind of look at the messages
it sends back and forth. But essentially
like the way you can think about this is
this is not just claude code giving you
a result. It's claude code talking to
claude code talking to claude code to
get your thing done. I think you get the
point. It just keeps going like this and
it does that while keeping this entire
to-do list in mind. Okay. So, it also
manages its to-do. And then also, as
you've seen before, we have these
different ways of dynamically adding
even more context and really engineer
our context to our advantage with
different tools in here. The one tool I
showed you so far is the context 7 MCP
where it pulls the freshest
documentations and adds that. So, when
we did that, it wasn't just considering
the prompt I was giving. It was also
considering the claw.md and the to-do or
more like the plan in that case that it
had at that point cuz it had the entire
chat history too. But it was also
considering the context from the context
7 MCP. And all of a sudden that's a lot
of information. That's a lot of rich
information to actually do something. In
contrast to you doing the same thing in
GPT5 and it then going ahead and giving
you an answer. This is a lot of concrete
info you're giving it. And the whole
system is set up to work for 5 minutes.
Sometimes I had it run for an hour or
two with some of the sub agents that
we're about to explain next here on its
own. You never get a 2-hour waiting time
in chat. just a whole different system
for a different purpose for users that
have more patience are ready to really
engineer the context and refine the
results rather than GPT5 being optimized
for outputs that are usable as is. Okay,
so over here you see the different types
of context and over here you can kind of
see the workflow as it goes. But
additionally to all these types of
context, there's one more thing that you
can do and that is set up custom agents
that add even more context and make your
request even more specific. Plus, they
come with other advantages like you can
force them to use specific tools because
they have a specific purpose. More on
that in the next section on MCPS. But if
you're using one of these sub agents,
which actually at this point I'm going
to show you visually because that just
makes it so much simpler. So, I'm just
going to open a project that I've been
working on recently here with some sub
aent setup. I'm just going to say claude
and then as I'm in here, I'm going to
say / agents. And as you can see, I have
multiple agents in here. So I have a QA
software tester, a AIAS backend
engineer, I have a versatile deployment
fixer, a code reviewer, front-end
webdev, and then a flux image generator.
You can see these are all different
agents. And you might be like, all
right, okay, so different agents. What
is that all about? Well, it's really
simple to create them. And I think
understanding them starts from this
creation because you say create new
agent and then it asks you, okay, do you
want to create this agent in this local
project or do you want to create your
personal agent generally in Claude?
Let's just do a personal one that is
going to be across all of my different
projects. And then what Enropic
recommends here is that you always start
by generating it with claude. So I'm
just going to pick the first version
here and then I can answer this
question. Describe what this agent
should do and when it should be used. So
specifically I'm going to create an
agent that is just there for expert
development documentation writer that
updates all documentation
including the clothd file. Okay. Going
to hit enter. It's going to use clots to
generate the agent setup file. And there
we go. We proceeded to step four where
it asks what tools does this agent want.
So you could just give it all tools. Or
if you go to the advanced options, you
can really see the full list. And you
could be very selective. You could, for
example, tell it, hey, I have no
interest in this one having these other
MCPS. Going to deselect this one and
this one. Can hide advanced options
again. Make it simpler. And then it can
keep all other tools. That's fine. And
then we're going to continue. And then
it's going to ask, okay, what model do
you want to use for this agent? As
writing out the documentation is pretty
simple. You could get away with using
the Haiku model here. That will eat up
the most credits and give you the most
mileage on your plan. In my case,
because I have the biggest plan, I'm
going to use Opus. I really like the
writing and the thinking and the
strategy of Opus. So, especially for my
documentation, I want this to be well
written. You can probably get away with
Haiku, though. And then I'll give it a
color. Uh, this one is going to be cyan.
Perfect. And there we go. The final
setup, our dev docs updater. There's a
description of him right there. There's
a system prompt. And we can just hit
enter right here. And rather than me
kind of like overexlaining this, let's
just look at the agent who's right here.
Devoc updator. You can see him. I can
navigate to him, hit enter, say edit
agent, and then open in editor. And then
it will open up a text editor with the
entire system prompt and the entire
instructions for the agent that Claude
came up with. And right here, this is
where we return to our little
visualization of what the agent does.
Because if you're using an agent, you're
not just giving it all of this context
right here. You're also giving it well
in this case the devd docs updater
markdown file but for our little
visualization here let's just write
agent because what really happens is all
of this gets added to your history and
all of a sudden this agent is executing
the task that you assign him to and
that's exactly what you can do. So now
if you do things and don't worry we'll
review this file in a second and what
the different sections mean. But when
you're actively working with clot code,
what you can now do is not just that you
have all of this context that you're
communicating to clot code and therefore
being really precise in what you want
and how you want it done, but also the
entire process changes because all of a
sudden instead of clot code just
interacting with itself and just
creating to-dos and doing things, you
can tell it more concretely, hey Claude,
I want you to work through the to-do
list, but once you're done, I want you
to spawn this devdoc updator and use
specifically that agent to update all of
my documents. So then clot code will
classically work with itself and itself.
But then once it's finished, it will
move and use this dev docs agent. I'll
just type a because I'm out of space
here. And it will use this specific
agent to do the specific task. Now on
the surface that might look trivial. You
could just say, okay, why can't I just
send this prompt to chat GPT after
having a bit of a conversation? Isn't
that the same thing? Well, if that's all
you're doing, yeah. But the point here
is that this does way more. Okay?
Because the structure here is the
following. At the top, you have a
description for other agents to
understand what this one is doing. And
it's really there to make the other
agents understand when they would want
to invoke aka activate this agent. So
here it says, "Use this agent when you
need to create, update, or maintain
development documentation, including
readme files, cloud MD files, API
documentation, blah blah blah blah
blah." Then down here is a list of all
the tools it has including MCPs. So we
gave it access to the context 7 MCP. You
can see that right there. We select that
as an option, right? So it can actually
pull up the newest documentation to
write our own documentation reliably.
That's a great thing that you cannot
just do in chat GPT. And then down here
is the system prompt on how it should
behave. And this is the part you would
want to customize along with this
description if something there doesn't
sound right to you. But usually gets it
pretty right. But especially for agents
that you're going to be using regularly,
this is where prompt engineering, as
much as people dislike the word at this
point, is necessary because, well, this
is where the magic happens. This is
where you define the behavior of the
agent, the rules that it lives by, and
this is where you can make changes. So,
Claude did an excellent job at this
agent building prompt in the background.
So, usually what you get right here is
an incredible starting point and all you
need to do is make a few minor tweaks.
But if you want to change how it handles
Claude MD files right here, then you
could make that right in this section.
And then if you make any changes to the
file, you want to resave this, close out
of it, and your agent will be updated.
And then just to demo this right away in
this other project, I actually just
realized that I haven't updated the claw
and def file today on the changes that
I've done. So use the documentation
agent to update my documentation. Hit
enter. And then in a second, we should
see the sign agent spawn in here. and
cloud code actively using that agent
with the tools that it has assigned to
it and the system prompt that we just
updated to do it. And here you can see
it dev docs updater it's already doing
it and updating the documentation for
this project right here and that's the
very basics of how agents work. Now the
cool thing is if you set up multiple
agents you can say things like okay I
want you to build the front end with the
front end engineer then I want you to
connect the back end with the back end
engineer then I want you to use the
testing agent to test the entire app and
then in the end use the devdocs updater
to update the entire documentation of
the working app that the other free
agents built and you hit enter and you
go get a coffee and 3 hours later you
come back and the whole thing happened.
Now in practice you might have to
confirm a few commands in between but
that's how it works. But at this point,
I do want to talk about when to use
these agents cuz it's actually not so
obvious and from my experience, I don't
think you should be using an agent for
every single thing you can. Now, this is
maybe more of advanced concept, but
nevertheless, I want to kind of squeeze
it in here because if you work with
agents, it's important to understand
that when you spawn agent one and he
goes off and does all of this work,
okay? And then, let's say it's a
research agent with access to the
internet and it researches various sites
and pulls them together and creates a
summary for you. Then the research agent
will have an output. It will create this
research text that is maybe this long.
It's just a fraction of the work it did,
right? Like that's the whole point. You
don't want every single detail of what
the agent did. Well, if you then take
the research agent and you hand it off
to a writing agent and yeah, at this
point it's hopefully starting to click
that you can use these agents for more
than just development. You could use
them for any workflow that you already
have in CHP to recreate your prompts
with agents and then let them
collaborate. But if you do that again
it's important to realize that if agent
one produces this research document this
output when it hands its work to the
next agent or to claude code the kind of
main agent the orchestrator as you can
think of him then it only hands off the
result and not the entire process. In
many cases like if you have a research
agent that's fantastic. If you have an
agent writing documentation that's
incredible you don't want the entire
fault process handed off to the next
agent. The beautiful thing about these
agents is they have independent context.
So, right here, agent one has 200,000
tokens of context as of now. They
released the update to the Sonnet API
recently with 1 million tokens, but as
of now, it's not live yet, depending on
when you're watching the video. That
might be the case already. But the point
is, each agent has its own context
window, meaning its memory is limited.
It cannot just intake every book in the
world into its context. There's only so
many words it will take. And it uses
that context to do all of this work
right here. But then it produces a
report that, let's say, is maybe just a
few thousand tokens. and it hands that
off to the next agent which takes over.
So here we have agent two and maybe
agent two is a writer and again this
agent has another 200,000 tokens of
context and it takes in this report
which is amazing cuz now it has a
summary of everything that it needs to
know to then go ahead and work again on
a final I don't know let's say blog post
and then it writes its blog post with
all the context it has including this
report and then voila you have your
final blog post and this worked great.
So at this point you might be asking
what are the advantages of using an
agent over just using clot code as is.
Well there's a few. One of them is you
can give specific agents specific tools.
So you can make our agent read only so
that doesn't have the ability to create
or delete files which can be
advantageous in some situations. Also,
you can assign certain MCPS to just a
certain agent, not to overwhelm claude
code. Because if you have a bunch of
MCPS, you can assign one to each agent
and then just invoke that agent when you
need that MCP. And you know that you set
up the agent with all the instructions
of how to really use that MCP. So, for
example, if you want the backend
engineer that uses context 7 every time
in the prompt, you can specify and
claude code gives you this advice of
using the word proactively. So if you're
in the process of refining that agent's
prompt, you can say proactively use the
context 7 MCP to verify all the planning
you do. And then every time it plants,
it will use context 7 on its own. You
can do this with any MCP. Really
powerful. Beyond that, you can pick
which model to use. And by far my
favorite thing is you can chain or run
agents in parallel. So let's abstract
away from coding for a second because
you can use cloth code for way more than
that. People are using it to write to
build design studios all of these other
tasks that you might already be doing
inside of chat manually by copy pasting
prompts. Well, you can set up agents
here and kind of chain them together.
So, how that looks practically as we
illustrated before with chatpt you put
in a prompt with some extra context and
you get a result as it works for it.
Maybe it thinks maybe it uses some
tools. With clot code, you get a whole
lot more context as we discussed with
the cloud MD file and all these extra
agent prompts etc. And also the work
process is different. That's clot code
talking with clot code talking with clot
code creating a plan talking with 20
more instances of clot code. So it kind
of works with itself and then gives you
the result. And now when we introduce
agents well yet again this looks
differently because it's just clot code
talking with I'm just going to say agent
one and then if you chain them together
it can be agent one doing its work and
talking to agent two. And to keep this
simple then you would get the result.
Now to be clear, even the agent works
with itself and uses this clot code
engine to kind of go through things and
work through them. Doesn't just give you
the results straight away. But this is
really cool because if you, for example,
set up a researcher agent and you give
it an MCP that can browse the web, well
then the researcher agent can go out and
find different pieces of information and
create a report for you that it then
hands over to the second agent, which
might be a blog writing agent. And then
the blog writing agent does one thing.
It writes the blog for you, which you
then get as a result. And that's
beautiful. You can change this together.
In ChachiPD, you would have to do
multiple steps, right? You run a deep
research and then you run a block
writing prompt and then maybe you follow
up and refine that. You can have all
that baked into your prompt writing
agent with some criteria for a good
outcome and it will kind of reprompt
itself and keep working on itself until
it gets to a desired result as you
specified it in the prompt. Now this is
great but there's one more scenario
possible here and it's also the most
exciting one because you can kind of
start seeing the potential of this
versus an assistant like chatt because
what you can do is let's say you have
these two agents right you have agent
one which is the research agent and then
you have agent two which is the writing
agent and this is kind of the first
workflow that I showed you here right
but what you can also do is you can just
spawn three research agents like so and
then all three of them give their
reports to the writing agent as context
to consider and that agent will produce
the result. So it's not just that you
can chain these agents together, you can
also run them in parallel. And that's
where it gets incredible because once
you get one of them working in a way
that is productive to you, you can say
now spawn five and then hand all of that
work to agent number two to finish up
the task or you can create an entire
chain with actually more than two or
three steps. Right? You can see how many
possibilities you have here. And as I
said that both of our tasks finished up
here. On the one hand, my documentation
agent in this other project finished
writing the documentation including the
systems that I implemented today. So
that is really great. But this one will
close out for now. I just quickly wanted
to show you the agents feature. But the
most exciting part is the project that
we're building. This no machine is
really shaping up. As you can see, it
told us, okay, we completed almost all
of these tasks right here. No machine is
now successfully built and ready for
deployment. Okay, so here it catches me
up what we've accomplished. created a
nextjs web application with the
following features. This is the things
we talked about. Perfect. Technical
implementation. This is the stack it
plan for. Perfect. This is the project
structure. It outlined the plan. Also
great. And then here next steps and this
is how you use it. It communicates with
you just like chatpt. But it tells you
hey bro I did everything I could. These
are the next steps we need to do. To
complete the setup you will need to
that's me create a supper.com.
Set up the database schema provided in
cloud.md. get API keys for entropic and
file AI and configure environment
variables in env.local deploy to versel.
So let me explain this to you if you've
never encountered this before. So sepase
as I mentioned earlier is a site that
creates and manages databases. So on
there we'll be creating a database and
the way these production ready databases
work is usually they're in a language
that is called SQL. And essentially the
way it works is that Claude will write
up these files that you just need to
copy and paste into a specific point on
sapperabase.com. If you just copy paste
and then you hit the green button, it
will do all the actions for you and
you're set. Sounds easy. It also is
easy, but you do have to take these
steps manually. So let's do this by
opening up Sapperabase right here and
going to my dashboard. I'll go into my
pre-existing organization. And at this
point, let me just review this. Create a
supperase project at sapperabase.com. So
I'm on supper.com and you can see this
new project button here. In case that is
not clear or maybe you're not sure how
to do something, you could say, "Okay,
explain step one in detail." And then it
will really give you a click byclick
navigation. And as you'll see in a
second here, you could even give it
screenshots like this. On Mac, I'm
clicking command shift 4 to drag this.
And then I could go in here and say
CtrlV and it will paste this image in
here. And I can say the green new
project button question mark. And I can
talk to this as if I would talk to
chatbt. Right? It told me what to do.
Now I'm coming back with my feedback.
And in a second it's going to look at
the image and it should tell me, yeah,
it can see where I'm at. And new project
button is on the top left. Perfect. So
as you can see, you can really use it to
guide you through everything step by
step, even if you're not familiar. So
let's do this. Let's click new project.
And ah okay, I'm at a point where I only
have two projects live and I use supper
base and two projects on this account.
I'll just quickly upgrade so we can keep
going. But yeah, as I said on a free
plan, you can have two live apps. So
back to projects, gonna say new project.
Going to call this the no machine. One
best practice is to never use spaces. I
mean, you can, but if you can avoid it
with anything development related,
you're going to prevent things from
breaking here and there. It's just a
good best practice. I'm going to pick a
server that is close to me. I think
Western Europe, Paris sounds good. I'm
just going to give it a password and
create a new project. Say understand
here. And then here's the stuff that
I'll be needing in the next steps. The
project API keys and more. So let's go
back to cloud code. See what it wants.
Okay. Choose a project name. Set a
database password. Done. Done. Select a
region. Done. Pricing plan. Free tier
should be perfect for getting started.
Okay. Also sorted. After the project is
created, you'll get your next supper URL
and the anon key. Okay. And these files
you will need to add to your project.
And in case you're not familiar with
this locally, you want to manage these
in a so-called. Eenv file. Now this file
is hidden by default and on a Mac you
want to hit commandshift dot to show
hidden files. So here it is.local
and then also up here you can see a
cloud folder that is hidden. If you
create local agents they will be placed
in here. Anyway, right now we're working
with thev.local file. I'll say open with
text edit and right here I will copy in
the data. So what I need is the next
public supper URL and the next public
supper anon key and the supperase
service ro key. Okay, let's see if we
can get those from this site. So, if
you're on the project, what you want to
do is go here to the project settings on
the left side and then here you can find
API keys. Now, this can be confusing
sometimes because they had old API keys
and now they have new API keys. So, what
I'm just going to do is give a
screenshot of this to clot code and ask
which one of these do I set as? And then
I'm going to give it all the free keys
that it wants here in my file and then
I'll wait for the answer. While I do
that, I want to show you one little tip
on a Mac. And that is something a friend
of mine showed to me recently. And that
is if you hit commandshift 5, you can
change the settings of how these
screenshots are made. And usually what
you want is go to the options and then
save to clipboard instead of the desktop
or the documents folder cuz then it
doesn't just create new files every time
you take a screenshot. And you can kind
of just take screenshots and then paste
them in. This also works with chatbt,
cloud code, any other app. Just a really
good little tip to make a bit more
efficient and get through a process like
this setting up the database. So let's
see what did it say. The anom public key
is shown in the first section. So I copy
the anon key and then next public suppon
key I paste it in here with command v.
Then the supperase service ro key is the
one we need to reveal. So I'm going to
click reveal right here. Say copy and
paste that one in here under service ro
key. Then we're missing one, right? The
next public supper URL. You'll need to
go back to the main project setting to
get your project URL. Look for something
like your project ID.appabase.co. Go to
project settings and general in the left
sidebar. Okay. So let's go to project
settings in general. Look for project
URL or reference ID. Okay. So project
ID. It's this right here. Right. So I'm
going to copy this. And this is my Sappa
base URL. Ah, it actually wants the URL,
not just the ID. So I only have this
project ID. I could insert it into here.
But again, if I'm not sure, I'm just
going to tell it what I'm not sure
about. Here is the project ID, but the
URL looks different. I'll say project ID
colon and then paste it. And then I
always separate things with comma.
That's the simplest way. Here my project
URL looks like this up here. So I'll
give it that project URL and then I'll
paste it in here. Let's see what it has
to say. Ah, and now it's proactively
actually fixing the file for me. Okay.
So it's changing it from just ID to
yeah, the format it told me about. Okay.
Okay, so if I close this file again and
reopen it, I guess Claude made the
changes for me now. Yeah, there you go.
So, see this is how you kind of do
things that you have no idea how to do.
Claude can assist you and do it for you
and it will many times. So, there's a
few more things here and it tells you
perfect. Now, your supper configuration
is correct. Next step to complete, you
need these two API keys and you need to
set up the database schema. So, let's
first do the database schema. And this
is simply explained. Honestly, you don't
need to understand this. You just have
to know that these SQL databases,
they're set up by running what's called
uh SQL schema. And the good thing is
clot code will write these for you. So
it'll tell you we'll need to go to the
SQL editor in your subbase dashboard and
run the schema. So what I'll do is I'll
just copy this schema right here. Copy.
And then in my application, I will go
into the SQL editor right here on the
left. And here I will paste. And as this
is pasted, I will hit run. And that's
it. That's our entire database set up.
If you're curious, you can go over here
to the table editor and see the
databases that it created right here. We
have favorites and we have different
boundaries. And then that's the database
setup for now. So there's any troubles,
we'll return to this and we can run new
schemas, but it's all connected. We can
close this file unless there's two more
things that we want here. But these are
not database related anymore. So this
completes the database setup for now. It
also wants the two API keys. So we want
the entropic API key and the file API
key. So in the case of entropic you need
to go to the empropic console and you
need some dollars on your account and
here I can create a new key say default
and say no machine add a new key copy
this key paste it right after where it
says enthropic API key and then I need a
file API key which is really simple when
you have accountant file and you load
some money into it here you just go to
the API keys tab and you can easily
create a brand new one which I'll call
no machine here I can copy the key and
over here I'll paste it right after file
API key equals. Okay, if I save over
this file and close it out, we're all
set up with the different AI connections
and database connections. And the good
news is you set this up once, it just
works. Your app has access to these
things now. So, I'll say all done and
let's see what is next. I'm a little
impatient here. So, I'm going to go up
and see what it wanted from me before.
And it says, yeah, it's actually ready
to run the application once we have
this. So, it says, "Excellent. You're
all set up. Let's test the no machine
application now. So, it's starting a
development server here. And you can see
that down here. This is also a new
feature they added recently. It can run
these processes in the background like a
development server that's just running.
So, you don't have to go to the online
version right away. You can kind of just
check it out locally and make quick
changes and update it. And then next up,
we'll also be getting this whole thing
live. But first, we need it to work
locally. Okay, so it's running. I can go
to this URL, localhost 303, and let's
see how this actually does. Okay, that
looks good. There's a login and a sign
up. Let's see. So, I'll fill this out
with a burner email of mine. Ooh, the
color is not great on here. This is all
stuff we can adjust in a second. Create
a email and a password. Check email to
continue signin process. So, my guess is
this will not work cuz we didn't connect
it to any email service. So, I can just
copy this and tell it like, okay, it
tells me to check email to continue
signin process, but there is no email.
And then sometimes you run into things
like this. It's like, okay, it
overthought the app. It made it really
complex. It forgot to implement the
whole email sending thing. And it will
fix that now. And as we do that, you
might notice here in the bottom right
corner right here, context left until
autocomplete 4%. So it's running out of
its 200,000 tokens of context here. And
as it hits that context window, it will
run this compact function that will
compress the entire conversation into a
very short file that it will pass to a
new conversation. In the interface, it
will look fluent, but really you'll be
losing most of the detail of what is
happening. So that is one thing to watch
out for, especially if you're in the
middle of some big change. Sometimes
running out of context can be disruptive
because it loses all the details of what
you were doing. It just passes the
summary to the new one. Just something
to be aware of. So it tells me, okay,
this is common with Sappa. It requires
email confirmation. Let's disable this
for development so you can test the app
immediately. Go to authentication
settings and disable this. And hold up.
Wait, that means I should have actually
Yeah, I received the email. Okay, so
this is completely my bad. I was using a
different off service on my other app
and I didn't even realize. Yeah. So, if
you set up supper, it's going to send
these emails so I can kind of just
confirm and it should work. My bad. So,
there you go. I just wanted to show you
the legitimate process of how I work
with this. So, yeah, includes little
hiccups like that, too. Let's see. This
just keeps loading. And I see the issue
here. So, it's redirecting me to
localhost 3000, but the server it's
running on is 300 free. So, let's just
see. This might just work actually at
this point. Let's see.
eagerpilm@gmail.com
password that I typed in login and it
worked. So yeah, we're logged in. The
authentication worked. The email
confirmation worked. Now, obviously,
this text is not optimal. I can barely
see this. We'll repair this in a second
here. But we can kind of give it a first
shot. No. See if this works. So, what's
the scenario here? Invitation to a
birthday party. Generate boundaries. And
let's see. Do our AI features work? No,
they don't. Fail to generate boundaries.
Please try again. Okay. And this is
where we get into fixing things. So,
let's talk about how to fix things like
this and how to improve. What you want
to do is you want to give it the error
message and tell it when I share
boundary I get and then quotation marks
the error message and then what also
really helps is if you say console and
then you copy the console into this. So
this is something you need to learn if
you are going to work with cloud code in
Google Chrome. Here you can right click,
say inspect, and then up here you want
to tab over to console. And then this is
basically what the web app has been
doing. And this console shows any errors
and stuff. And this is really helpful to
improve on what it is doing. So what you
want to do here is click anywhere in the
text and just rightclick and say copy
console. And we're just going to paste
that entire console log into here. Now,
to be clear, there's also MCPS to kind
of automate this. But again, we're
building our first thing. We're getting
things done. And then further down the
line as you learn more, you can automate
things like copying the console over. So
I just sent that message and now it's
just a matter of patience for it to fix
the issue. Sometimes it takes three,
four, five different iterations of this
and it just doesn't work. Doesn't work.
Doesn't work. But you'll make it work
anyway. And in the resource that I
included with this, I also included an
extra prompt to really find solutions
that might not be obvious at first
because sometimes you get stuck.
Sometimes you try this process 10 times
in a row and you still can't fix it. In
that case, I included a special extra
prompt that does this. Now, to be clear,
I got this somewhere off Twitter like a
year ago, but it has been a blessing
because it just shows you multiple
avenues to finding a solution. So,
again, that's included in the little
cheat sheet I prepared to accompany this
video. And right there, it tells me,
okay, the main issue is insufficient
credits on your anthropic API account.
Aha. Is that true though? If I look at
my enthropic API account billing, I see
there's $100 of balance. Okay, so I'll
just tell it actually there is $100 in
the account. Meanwhile, I will test out
this new version of the app and just say
invitation to a birthday party barely
visible, but I'll just generate
boundaries again. Maybe a little
refresh. So, it updates for the new
code. Failed to generate boundaries.
Please try again. Okay. Um, let's have a
look. What's the issue here? So, the
error from the console was saying it's
an invalid request error. Your credit
balance is too low to access the
entropic API. It's giving me some tips
on how I can verify if this is the right
key. So, API keys. Yeah, I'm in the
right organization. Okay, I would say
let's just try again. So, I'm going to
refresh the page. Describe the boundary
scenario. Invitation to a birthday party
and generate boundaries. Let's see.
Okay. So, I have a suspicion here
because there's money there. This might
not be an issue with my credits, but
with the way it implemented the API. So,
I'm just going to say this, use context
7 to verify the enfor
API implementation. And this way, you
can also prompt MCP servers. You don't
need agents with the MCP servers to use
them. You'll see that it'll engage it
right here because we have it installed.
You can already see it pulled in 2,000
lines of anthropic documentation and the
implementation looks correct. So, that's
good. And as you can see right here, it
ran out of context. So, it's going to
compact the entire conversation and kind
of start a new one with a summary of
everything we did. In this case, it's
fine. We're not in the middle of
something big. So, I'm really confused
by why this doesn't work. This should
kind of just work. So, give me a minute
here to figure out what's wrong. And
I'll be back in a second. Okay. Okay, so
now after giving it a screenshot of this
page and this page, I asked it, "Hey,
I'm doing what you tell me and it's
still not working." It figured out on
its own that it was actually using some
old key that it had caged in the
browser. I didn't even know where that
old key came from. But my point is with
these two screenshots, it managed to
hopefully fix it. And now our
application should be working because it
also tested the API and it works now
apparently. Let's see. Invitation to a
birthday party. Generate boundaries.
failed to generate boundaries. Okay,
maybe I need to refresh one more try.
Failed to generate. Okay, so again,
inspect, open the console. I'll copy the
console and say still doesn't work. And
honestly, this is the reality of the
process. But the good news is all of
this stuff is figure outable and I
haven't arrived at a problem yet that I
wasn't able to solve. And also take this
little scenario as a piece of advice to
not overengineer your apps from the
beginning. Rather create the simplest
version possible. make sure that that
works reliably and then add on top of
it. That's a really good piece of advice
by the way. And again, always make sure
to use the plan mode when you do that or
when you add big features. Ah, so cloud
code is telling me here that hey, the
server is still using the old API key.
The environment shows it's loading, but
somehow it's not picking up the new key.
Let me check if there's a issue. Okay,
do your thing cloud code. Just fix it.
But as you can see with the info from
the console, it usually is able to
figure this out quite well. When in
doubt, add screenshots. Okay, so now it
took the app offline on this port 3000
free and it ran a new server on the port
3000. So that essentially mean it's the
same URL but just 3000 instead of 3000
free. And then I get an error here. I
can just copy this error and paste it in
here and hit enter and it will fix that
too. And yeah, this is the reality of
fixing bugs. I mean, we're building a
custom application with multiple AI
integrations all in one shot. Might just
take a few of these little bug fixing
rotations. Remember the process is
always similar. It's clot code does
something. Say it creates a page but
then something might not work. So what
you want to do is you want to take a
screenshot. I'll try to draw a camera
here. That's the flash. How did I do?
Does that look like a camera? Fair
enough. And you also want to add what's
in the console and feed that back into
clot code which will then improve the
app. And the cycle continues. So it
fixed it right here. So let's have a
look. The no machine had a new look
there for a second but there's another
error. So, I'm going just copy that and
paste it back in. What's going on here,
Claude? Make this work. So, we can get
to the fun part here, which is some
final notes on MCPS and actually getting
this live on the web. Right now, it's
combobulating. And if we refresh, voila,
it just fixed it. I'm not even sure how,
but that's okay. So, the no machine.
Okay, we can start getting boundaries
right here. I need to sign in again.
Fair enough. Okay, we definitely have to
fix this text in a second here, but
there it is. So, a birthday invitation.
Generate boundaries. Ooh, it's loading
this time. Come on. You know you want
it. Yes, that's it right there. Okay, so
okay, we have a soft null, clear no the
wall, and it made four variations of the
wall. Okay, that's unexpected. And then
we can generate these images. Yes,
apparently it successfully picked out
the part of the prompt that generates
the images, too. So, let's see. So, the
first one is the soft no. Thank you so
much for thinking of me. Unfortunately,
I won't be able to make it this time. I
hope you have an amazing celebration.
Now, let's generate the image along with
that. Oh, and it errored out. That's
okay, though. Oh, we really got far
here. And we have the error here in the
console. So, we kind of just copy that
and tell clot code. Okay, that worked,
but the image generation failed.
Console. Then I paste the console.
Meanwhile, I want to try this again,
though. This is kind of fun. And I can
think about how I want to improve this
already. So, one thing definitely is
that I wanted this text to be easily
readable. But then I really like how it
splits it out. I really don't need six
responses. I only kind of need three
right here as I have the images. So, I
can prompt it to remove these three. And
then the reformed doormat note. Okay.
Remember, your time and energy are
precious. Saying no to one invitation
doesn't make you a bad friend. It makes
you a good friends to yourself. Your
mental health is worth more than any
awkward social moment. Okay, that's good
advice right there. Okay, cloth code
finished up. Okay, so now it should
work. Let's refresh the page. Uh,
birthday invitation. Generate
boundaries. Okay, let's generate the
first image. So, that would be thank you
so much for thinking of me.
Unfortunately, I won't be able to make
it. And then the visual concept is a
birthday cake with tiny white flag
sticking out. Laundry work Netflix
calling. Oh, that's actually so cute.
That's a great image to send along with
that message, you know. Okay, let's look
at the hard boundary. The wall. Thanks
for the invite, but I'll be passing on
this one. Ooh, that's a bit harsh. Well,
fair enough. I mean, that's the wall.
What is the image like for this one? Do
not disturb. I mean, that's kind of
good. Honestly, I really like how these
came out. So, now it's about refining
it. So, let's do the two main things
here. And also it has a save function.
Interesting. Kind of save. Okay. Can
also review my history. That's nice.
Okay. But let me share what's wrong. So
like first of all the text when I type
is barely visible. And if you do visual
things, I would recommend just including
screenshots. So I'll just screenshot
this and then paste it in here and then
let it work. So it will figure that out.
And probably increase the contrast by
changing the font color. Here it sees
that it's barely visible. Let me fix the
color. It's writing some code. And this
will be done in a second. And then
meanwhile I can prepare my next message.
It generates a total of six boundaries.
Whereas I just need three. And then in
brackets you can always add extra
context. This is just a classic prompt
engineering trick but it helps. So if
you want to make it more specific you
could say the last free red boundaries
can be removed. So perfect. I just
finished typing that as it finished the
first change. And I'm going to just
refresh and see how it works now. Ah,
text looks great. That works very well
for me. Let's see if it only shows three
cards as we're hoping for here. Drum
roll. Yeah. Ah, close. Okay, so it still
has four. I'll just give it a screenshot
and tell it there are four. Remove the
last red one, the wall. Hit enter again,
but it's getting closer already. And
then this remains functional. And at the
bottom, let's see. Let's do maybe the
middle one this time while we wait. The
clear. No, I appreciate the invitation,
but I won't be able to attend. I hope
you have a wonderful birthday. It's a
good balance. A calendar with the
birthday date circled dramatically in
red with a tiny stick figure running
away screaming. Nope. Okay, fair enough.
There's one. Kind of makes me want to do
one more while cloth code is jazzer
sizing. No entry. These are really good.
I like these visual concepts from the
model. And as you can see, it
implemented everything successfully.
Like it's making images with the file
API. It's generating these ideas with
the enthropic API. It's storing
everything in our database. If I go over
to our supper base, if I go to
boundaries, yeah, you can see these
different birthday invitation boundaries
being generated here. You have them all,
the soft responses, medium responses,
firm responses. It's parsing it out
correctly. It understood what we want to
do. They're all stored in here,
including the reformed doormat notes.
Okay. And all of that is happening
because Claude Code set it up
successfully. So, this is great. Final
test. Uh, wedding invitation. There it
is. Free boundaries ready to be copied.
Like so we can generate the images in
here. This is really everything I wanted
from the app. Remember the original
concept. I didn't even give it this
image, but it's exactly like that. 1 2 3
1 2 3. Thank you so much for thinking of
me. Unfortunately, I won't be able to
make it to the wedding. I'm sending all
my love and best wishes to you both. And
then this image with that. That's kind
of good. That's not bad. Let's do one
more to just verify all of this works. I
appreciate the invitation, but I won't
be able to attend the wedding. Thank you
for including me in your celebration.
Boundary ninja. Okay, I don't love that
part. Maybe I could tweak the prompt and
make sure it doesn't include the word
boundary in the images, but I'm pretty
happy with this as is. Next up, I could
work on the save function. And the way I
would do that is well, I would explore
my app. The history seems to work well,
but the save button doesn't seem to
work, so I'll just tell it. And then I
go through the same process as before.
But at this point, I won't bore you with
further refinements and adding features.
I think you see the point. If we want to
add a brand new functionality to the app
that is rather large, I would again
switch to the plan mode, refine the plan
until I'm happy and then implement that.
Additionally, I also want to highlight
that the claude MD file has been updated
in the process and we have project
details on the no machine right here.
So, it's always using that in the
context and if you want to make
architectural changes to the whole
thing, you could just go in here and
then clot will respect that in every
message it sends afterwards. Okay, but
now at this point while it's
implementing this fix to the safe
function, we really want to do one more
thing and that is get this onto the
internet. So how do we do that? Well,
the easiest way that almost everybody is
using that vibe codes is the following.
They use their own GitHub to store the
code. You can think of this as a online
hard drive for all your code and then
they link it up to Verscell that for
every new deployment on GitHub, it
deploys a new version of the site that
is then accessible via URL. So in order
for this to work for us, we need to get
our code on GitHub. Now there's many
ways to do that and a billion tutorials
on the web, but the most basic one would
be just going to the GitHub to your
repositories saying new and then naming
this and saying okay, this is the no
machine and then I'll make this one
public. You can access the code in the
description below in case you like my
app here and you want to extend it from
the point where it is right now. Make it
your own. You'll just have to change the
different keys in the env file as I
showed you. But like this, I created a
brand new repository. And then
practically what you want to do is and
what I recommended in the setup section
is you want to install the GitHub CLI.
Again, like I'm not going to go through
all of the setup step by step because
that would just make this video
unbearably massive, but installing the
CLI is pretty straightforward. And
again, you can consult CHPT in order to
help you with that. But the magical
thing that it allows you to do is that
from within here, sure the interface
might not be the prettiest thing in the
world, but it's so damn functional
because all of these developer tools are
just right here. They're right in there.
So, for example, with the GitHub CLI
already installed on my machine, now
that it implemented a fix for the save
button, which I'll just briefly test
before we put this live, I say my boss
has a wedding. Click generate boundaries
and then let's just see if that works.
And then let's get this live onto the
internet. Let's see. It's saving
boundaries saved to your history. Okay,
I guess that does something. Let's just
get this online. What I can do now
because I created the repository, I can
just say add this project to my GitHub
repository
and then I share the URL. Now, just to
be clear, you could also create the
repository from within here. I just kind
of showed you on the website, so it
makes more sense, but you could equally
say create a new repository for this
project on my GitHub, but you do need
the GitHub CLI for this. Otherwise,
you'll just have to take these files and
every other way that you can do this is
just so much more complicated and
cumbersome. And you'll be doing this all
the time. Whenever you add new features,
add new bug fixes, whatever. You always
want to add it to your GitHub because
then with Versell, it's just looking at
your GitHub and every time you add a new
version of the app, it just hosts a new
version of the app for you on the
internet. And then that whole process
becomes super simple. So, you get both
the versioning with GitHub. So every
time you add new changes, it creates
something that it calls a commit which
is essentially a new checkpoint. And if
something breaks with the code or you
make changes with cloud code and
something stops working, you know you
have every previous version on GitHub
and you can just easily return. So
that's why GitHub is absolutely
essential in this workflow. And then if
you link it to Versell, you
automatically will have a live website
as you'll see. So I'll just confirm this
a few times. Say yes. And yeah, looks
like it's finishing up the process. And
then we should see all our files appear
in our GitHub here in a second. If we
just refresh the no machine repository
again, these steps could be done
differently. You could be using the
GitHub desktop app, but just do this
from the get- go. It just works so well
cuz every time you have a new version,
you just say push and commit to Git and
it writes these beautiful commit
messages where it tells you what it
changed. So yeah, that's it. I just
confirm this and now it's adding it to
GitHub. So again, just for your
reference, whenever you change
something, you'll just say push and
commit to Git. After this is set up
once, you'll just be saying push and
commit to git or I guess you could just
say commit to git and then it's going to
add the new version of your code that
you worked on with plot code to your
GitHub as it did right here. So yeah, if
I head over and refresh, I should see
all the code appear here. Beautiful. The
entire app is in here with very detailed
instructions on what it does written by
AI and the whole app in here. So this is
wonderful. Now it's stored on my GitHub
and in case you wonder where those
versions are, well you go to these
commits here and you will see a commit
history here and then you can take this
commit number right here and just in
clot code you could say okay revert to
this version and it will go back to that
version discarding all the changes you
made after that. That can and probably
will be a lifesaver for you at some
point. It is for everyone trust me.
Okay, so now that we have the code on
GitHub successfully, one last step and
that is hooking that up to our Verscell
one time so that every time there's a
new commit, a new version of the site
gets actually hosted on the internet cuz
in GitHub we just store it. It's not a
live website that you could now access.
So in Verscell, I'm just going to go
into my account and said add new project
and then here import Git repository. As
I logged into Verscell, I immediately
connected it to my GitHub account and
now it lets me do this. I can pick my
git repository and we're looking for the
nom machine. Oh, there you go. It's at
the top. I can kind of just hit import
and I believe all the default settings
should be fine right here. I'll just say
deploy. And that's how simple it is. I
can already tell you we'll be needing to
do one more thing which is on Verscell.
We also need to transfer these
environment variables. Remember the env
file where we were adding the empropic
API key, file API key, the database
connections. We'll also have to put them
in here in a sec. But let's let this
deploy first and then we'll copy these
files over. So in our finder,
commandshift dot to expose the hidden
files. I'm going to open myv.local file.
And after this is done deploying, we can
add these keys to versel. Wonderful. So
this is deployed. Continue to the
dashboard. And then in this project, the
way you set up these environment
variables, again, this is a onetime
thing. You go to settings and then in
here it says environment variables. And
I'll just add exactly the ones that I
have in myv file. So next public supper
URL is the key and then the value is
what comes after the equal sign. Just be
careful that I copy this correctly that
I get every sign. Or alternatively, what
is even easier, you can just import the
env file. I just drag it onto here like
so and import all of this and it will
automatically bring in all the
environment variables like so. And I can
just say save and there they are. So now
my Verscell is set up with the
environment variables and we can look at
our deployment and see if this thing
actually works. So if I go to overview
here, it shows a preview of the site.
This is the main URL for the app. No
machine.verell.app.
And then we get some sort of error. So
now this gives us a chance to do a final
troubleshooting run in cloud code to
push it to GitHub to for it to show up
on the internet. So we're getting this
error. Now what do we do? As per usual,
we pull up clot code and I'll say what I
did. deployed through Verscell. Now I
get and then I'm just going to copy this
error and also as per usual just get
used to doing this every time. I could
copy the console logs. Okay, there's no
console logs so we'll keep it as is. And
it says this is a common versell
deployment issue with middleware. Let me
help you fix this. And then it does its
thing. Okay, it's saying that's likely
because it doesn't have the environment
variables but we actually already did
that. So let's check again environment
variables. Yeah, that should be all
good. Okay, and it automatically decided
to commit to git. You could always see
that right here and by this little
generator with claude comment under the
commit. So I'll just say yes. So it's
higglypiging right now. I love these
sometimes. And then it goes straight
from my app into GitHub and then that
will automatically start a new
deployment here on Verscell. So in case
it doesn't start a new deployment, we
can always go to the settings of the
project here, go to git and then this
should be enabled. So if it's linked in
here, then every new commit will launch
a new deployment in here. Ah, and you
can see it appear just here. It's going
to build the site, which will take a few
seconds, and then we can check out the
new version of it. While it does that,
we can also double check GitHub just for
your understanding because right here
you will see we already have free
commits. See, this is the new one minute
ago. And yeah, as I said, every time
this appears, it will just push it to
Verscell. Excellent stuff. Ah, right
there it finished up. And we can kind of
preview our app just by clicking the
preview. And you'll see there's always
two links. There's this one right here
which is just this version of the app
and then there's kind of a main one that
you can share around and also for your
understanding the main one will always
go to the production app that is the
current version and then this concrete
link will change every time. So if you
want to share it with a friend or
colleague you just share this one and
then the newest version is always going
to update to that. And if you just want
the one to the current version then you
would share this link. Okay, doesn't
matter. In this case it's the same. I'm
going to use my login from before. Oh, I
still didn't change the text right here,
but I think at this point you understand
how you do that. And then I'm just going
to log in. That works. My boss has a
wedding. Generate boundaries. Let's see
if this works. This is the live
application right on the web that you
could access to. It worked. Okay,
perfect. Thank you so much for thinking
of me. I won't be able to make it. Let's
test the image generation on this one.
This one. This one. I guess that kind of
works. Yeah, there you go. Free images.
Boundaries right here. Boundary saved to
history. I mean, I guess that kind of
works. It saves everything to history,
but I could further refine that. But
there you go. That's the entire
application live on the internet. We did
it. I think that with the knowledge that
I gave you here, you're really able to
build a ton. And I want to round this
out with kind of next steps and what to
think about next. Okay. So, first of
all, if you want to redo this again,
check out the first link in the
description with my little cheat sheet
with all the prompts and resources and
some agents that I use and MCPS that I
would recommend. And as we kind of
completed the whole process here and hit
the entire checklist that I promised you
in the beginning from talking you
through the setup, introducing you to
agents, talking about MCPs, going
through the whole debugging cycle, and
making sure you have a database
integrated and everything hosted on the
web. There's really two items that I
want to touch on in the end that I
didn't go really deep into because
they're a bit more intermediate, I would
say. Those are agents and MCPS. So, I
briefly showed you how to install MCP
with the context 7 MCP. Installing MCPS
is super straightforward. It always
looks like that. And we talked about
agents extensively in theory, but then
here in practice, I actually want to put
them to work. So, I'm going to pull up
clot code one more time here. And I'm
going to say / agents here. And let's
see what we have here. So we have one
user agent which is a flux image
generator agent a general one and just
for the purpose of this demo we're going
to create one in this project. So we
went through the setup previously so I
don't need to explain everything. We're
just going to say generate with claude
right here. We want the agent that is a
QA tester which is essentially a quality
tester for apps in the development
industry. A QA tester that tries to
break my application. And I'll hit
enter. And then as you'll see in my
cheat sheet one of the free MCP servers
that I would recommend you begin with is
one that is called Playright. And I
could and I might create an entire video
just on this, but this is such a
powerful MCP server. It's kind of the
go-to for browser remote control and it
does literally that. So if you scroll
down here on the GitHub, you can go to
clot code and this one line will install
that MCP in my folder. So my sub agent
is set up. I'll just give it all the
MCPS for now. It's okay. The QA tester
can use Sonnet. That's fine. We'll give
it a green color. And that's it. That's
my agent right there. I'll hit enter. So
when I escape out of this now I have
some basic agent that claude generated.
I will also run this cloud MCP at
playright and that will add the MCP
server to my cloud. And here's the
interesting thing. Okay, so there's a
ton of MCP servers and most of them are
not worth your attention but in my
little cheat sheet I included the three
of them that I use all the time and that
I also recommend playright being one of
them. And the amazing thing about this
is it allows clawed code to use the MCP
to open up a new tab with your app and
then actually use that app. And if
something breaks, it knows about it
right away. So it can kind of try
different things. And if something
doesn't work out, the QA tester agent
gets all the console logs from that and
can deliver a report to Claude code on
what doesn't work so that Claude can fix
it. And as I added that, it's already
telling me, okay, since you added a QA
breaker agent and added Playright, these
are great tools for testing your no
machine app. Let's see if this is
available right away. I'm actually not
sure if I say MCP. Nah, it's not
available yet, right? You only see the
context 7 server that we installed
earlier. So I'm just going to close out
and open up new version of clot code.
And now the MCP should be active. So if
I say /mcp, ah, still not active. So
I'll run the command once more. And I
think I need to restart Claude to see
that. There it is. Play right. Perfect.
So now I can say / agents. And if I go
to my agents, I don't see my QA tester.
So I guess I'll just have to recreate
him. That's okay. QA tester agent that
tries to break my app. It will write
instructions that will most likely be
fine here. there. And then I just want
to make sure it has access to the
Playright MCP. So here if I go to
advanced, it will show me the full list
of all the tools. Again, you don't need
to know all of this. Just here under MCP
service. Maybe I can switch off the
context 7 MCP server cuz it really does
not need that. And then I go up and say
continue. For the QA tester, I think set
will be completely fine. Okay. Hit
enter. So now I have the agent right
here, the QA breaker. Beautiful. So if I
go on him, I can say edit agent, open an
editor. And then here's the entire agent
that was created. And here's the final
tip that I wanted to share. Like if you
go in here, this first part as I
mentioned earlier is for other agents to
pick when to activate this one. So this
we don't need to edit. But down here we
have the system prompt. And if you want
this agent to always use playright, then
we should alter this. You're an elite QA
engineer and penetration tester
specializing in breaking web
applications. Your mission is to think
like both a malicious user and an edge
case explorer. Here we can say
proactively
using playright to uncover hidden bugs.
So this wording is actually recommended
by Enthropic. If you say proactively
using and then a name of a MCP server,
you're going to see this agent using
that MCP server all the time if not
always. And that's one change you can
make. And another one in other agents
that is super useful, not for this one,
is you can kind of just add a new title
in markdown and say something like extra
context. And then if you want to give it
some specific documentation, you could
just paste it in here. You could just
throw any extra context that the agent
should have down here. So in this case I
don't need that but this is just an
extra tip for building agents. One of
the most useful things you can just take
an entire documentation and just paste
it into the agent that you know he knows
about everything. Doesn't need to use
context 7. He just knows. So if I save
and close out of this then that's it.
Then we have our little QA breaker
agent. And now you can do a few things.
As I showed you before in the drawing,
you could tell it fix XYZ and then use
the QA breaker agent to test it and it
will first do the fix with Claude and
then use the QA breaker agent. Or you
could do something like this. Use free
QA breaker agents to test the app. Now,
I think concretely with testing the app,
this doesn't make the most sense in the
world. This is not something I've
actually done before. It might make
sense in theory. I mean, with a lot of
these things, you just have to try and
you'll see if it works for you. But as
you can see, it's spawning three
different agents simultaneously right
now that will all be using Playright to
test my application. Now, honestly, I
don't even know if I can be using three
copies of Playright at the same time.
Probably, but this is where
experimentation opens up. You could give
API access to these agents, right? You
could have a image generation agent. You
could have a video generation agent. You
could have a whole dev team. You could
have a marketing manager, a creative
director. Then a bunch of agents with
specific APIs to generate images and
generate copy. And then you have one
agent that has MCP that connects to your
own database so it can post blogs for
you. And then you can unleash your
entire marketing studio by letting them
collaborate. I mean, people are
experimenting with this stuff, okay?
They're turning the promps they have in
chat GPT into these agents, letting them
collaborate, letting them build things,
do things. People are not just using
this for development. But I think by
learning the development basics, you'll
understand how these things work
together, how cloth code works. And
yeah, now you can see these agents just
like opening up browsers and asking for
permissions of, hey, can I take uh
snapshots of the current page, etc. And
I have to like confirm that multiple
times cuz I have three agents running.
So I have to hit enter like six times.
Okay. And now it's doing its thing. It's
signing up with a test email address,
etc. I think you see the point. So, now
we really covered all of it. Setup
agents, MCPs, debugging, using
databases, putting it on the web. Again,
don't forget to get your little cheat
sheet with all the notes from this
lecture and my MCP and agent
recommendations in there. But that right
there was quite the process and you made
it all the way through. We might have
never met, but I'm actually kind of
proud of you because I know how much it
takes to sit for a long video like this.
But as I say always with all of these AI
tools and skills, they stack. Whatever
you learned in chat GPT will apply to
editing the agent prompts in here.
Whatever you learned in automation,
well, you can connect all the
automations up to either agents or you
can trigger them within your
applications. If you follow the weekly
show on the channel, AI news you can
use. Well, we talk about new apps and
APIs and models all the time. Those can
inspire you in order to use your
prompting skills and vibe coding skills
to spawn new agents and use them in
parallel just like I am right here. All
of this stacks and creates a smoother
transition into a new technological era
for that most people won't be prepared.
But you being here at the end of this
video gives me confidence in the fact
that you'll be able to adjust to
whatever is coming cuz 99.99%
of the people don't have the patience
and the curiosity to be exploring new
skills like this. So with that being
said, I hope this was helpful. If you're
looking to hang out with other people
who do this type of stuff, that's
literally why we built AI advantage
community. We have extra spaces for Vibe
coding. People are sharing the apps
they're building. You could get
personalized support from my team on
this process. And just a few days ago, I
ran an event where I showed two new
workflows, both involving agents and the
custom app that I built. But all of that
kind of builds on what you just consumed
here. So, make sure you're solid on
this. And if you want to go further, the
Advantage community is there for you.
And with that being said, that's
literally all I have right now. Go and
build something and you might just
realize how creative, fun, and addictive
it can be.